a false positive It's
almost like a And
it's very scary when
we cross that data
because when we found
our biggest significant markups
our biggest outcomes that
drive fund returns a
lot of them were
just ideas They start
all had very little
traction But what else
did they have is
that they had a
business model that you
can call them copycats
but not essentially copycats
but they already have
a of references that
sized up the that
made it a more
familiar of a business
model So if you
can get in at
those types of companies
patterns and that kind
of how we invest
in today we're not
totally attracted by just
traction alone We need
to make sure that
this traction is you
to somewhere big I'll
kind make it crispy
the way of saying
it is like this
It's easy to find
a good idea but
it's a harder to
a big idea Not
all good ideas are
big ideas right So
that's kind of like
one big lesson from
our decade of